hello everybody just wanted to welcome
you to our first January Monday mocha in
this publication you'll find everything
that you need to know about what's going
on as far as classes here at Metro and
also within the company events that
we're having a few things about the
great agents that you share your office
with and also opportunities to share out
in the community also I put a few links
Ellie and I have put a few links
together for you that should be fun and
informative and you'll find those things
at the bottom of the publication if you
have any suggestions of things that
you'd like to see in next week's Monday
mocha let us know thank you very much
and happy selling